Register of the Socialist Workers Party Records, 1928-2002
Wisconsin Historical Society
- Part 1 (Micro 596, Micro 816, Micro 993, Micro 1078, Micro 2015, Micro 2050, AC 588, CB 131): Original Collection, 1928-1993, Micro 596; 185 reels of microfilm (35mm) and 2 films
  - Publication Records
    - Library
      - Education for Socialists, Micro 816
        - 1983, March - 1985 (Reel 91, Frame 1)
      - Information Bulletin
        - International Bulletin of the Fourth International, 1937, Micro 596 (Reel 25, Frame 231)
          - 1986, Numbers 1-2, Micro 2015 (Reel 72, Frame 878)
          - 1988, Number 1 (Reel 74, Frame 925)
          - 1989, Numbers 1-4 (Reel 76, Frame 304)
          - 1990, Numbers 1-5 (Reel 79, Frame 474)
          - 1991, Numbers 1-29 (Reel 82, Frame 371)
          - 1992-1993, July, Micro 2050 (Reel 91, Frame 138)
      - Internal Bulletin
        - Communist League of America, Micro 596
          - 1932, Numbers 1-5 (Reel 14, Frame 715)
          - 1933-1934, Numbers 6-17 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
        - Marxist Policy Committee, 1937 (Reel 15, Frame 339)
        - Organizing Committee for the Socialist Party Convention, Numbers 1-5, 1937-1938 (Left Wing Correspondence, December 1937, January 1938) (Reel 15, Frame 383)
        - SWP
          - 1938, Number 5-1940, Volume II, Number 13 (Reel 15, Frame 447)
          - 1940-1945, Volume III, Number 1-Volume VII, Number 6 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
          - 1945-1949, Volume VII, Number 7-Volume X, Number 6 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
          - 1949-1950, Volume XI, Number 1-Volume XII, Number 4 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
          - 1951, August, Volume XIII, Number 1 (Reel 18, Frame 437)
          - 1953, Volume XV
            - Numbers 1-10 (Reel 18, Frame 600)
            - Numbers 11-20 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
          - 1954, Volume XVI, Numbers 1-2 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
          - 1956-1959, Volume XVII, Number 1-Volume XX, Number 11 (Reel 20, Frame 55)
        - Workers Party, 1935-1936, Micro 596 (Reel 15, Frame 181)
      - Internal Information Bulletin, SWP
        - 1964 (Reel 23, Frame 194)
        - 1966, July (Reel 23, Frame 923)
        - 1967 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
        - 1968, June - 1969 (Reel 24, Frame 338)
        - 1970 (Reel 24, Frame 600)
        - 1971, Micro 816 (Reel 40, Frame 756)
        - 1972-1974, August (Reel 41, Frame 1)
        - 1974, August - 1975 (Reel 42, Frame 1)
        - 1976, July - 1977, Micro 993 (Reel 56, Frame 1)
        - 1981-1984, Micro 1078; Name changed to Information Bulletin in 1984. (Reel 69, Frame 541)
      - International Bulletin
        - Communist Left Opposition, Micro 596
          - 1931, Numbers 1-10 (Reel 24, Frame 721)
          - 1933, Number 17, Numbers 2-3 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
        - Information Service of the Fourth International, Volume 1, Number 1-Volume III, Number 1, 1940-1945 (Reel 25, Frame 267)
        - International Executive Committee of the Fourth International, Volume 1, Number 1, 1935 (Reel 25, Frame 239)
        - League of Communist Internationalists, Numbers 1-2, 1934 (Reel 25, Frame 147)
      - International Information Bulletin
        - National Committee of the Workers Party, Numbers 1-3, 1935-1936 (Reel 25, Frame 164)
      - SWP (Boletin de Informaciones Internacionales)
        - 1946-1951 (Reel 25, Frame 444)
        - 1952-1966 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
        - 1968-1970 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
        - 1971-1972, Micro 816 (Reel 40, Frame 465)
        - 1973-1974, Micro 2050 (Reel 92, Frame 1)
        - 1976, February - July, Micro 993 (Reel 55, Frame 691)
      - International Internal Information Bulletin
        - 1977-1980, Not published in 1978. (Reel 55, Frame 464)
        - 1982, 1985, Micro 1078 (Reel 69, Frame 422)
      - International Internal Discussion Bulletin
        - 1973, Volume X, Micro 816 (Reel 42, Frame 109)
        - 1974-1975, Volume XI-XII (Reel 43, Frame 1)
        - 1976-1978, Volume XIII, Number 1-Volume XV, Number 6, Micro 993 (Reel 56, Frame 343)
        - 1978-1980, Volume XV, Number 7-Volume XVII, Number 1 (Reel 57, Frame 1)
        - 1982-1985, Volume XVIII-XXI, Micro 1078 (Reel 70, Frame 1)
      - Party Builder
        - 1944-1947, Volume I, Number 1-Volume IV, Number 2, Micro 596 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
        - 1970, Volume VI (Reel 31, Frame 485)
        - 1972-1975, Volume VII-IX, Micro 816 (Reel 43, Frame 298)
        - 1976, Volume X, Micro 993 (Reel 57, Frame 216)
      - Party Campaigner, 1960-1964, Micro 596 (Reel 31, Frame 405)
      - Party Organizer
        - 1977-1980, Volume I-IV, Micro 993 (Reel 57, Frame 236)
        - 1981-1985, Volume 509, Micro 1078 (Reel 70, Frame 445)
      - Reports on Youth Work of the Fourth International, 1-4, 1969, Micro 2050 (Reel 92, Frame 558)
      - Research Bulletin (National Education Department), Numbers 1-3, 1941 (Reel 92, Frame 707)
      - Young Marxist, 1948-1949 (Reel 92, Frame 798)
  - Education Files
    - Chicago Marxist-Leninist School (Glotzer course), undated (Reel 76, Frame 1)
    - Cook County Branch Forum (Goldman lecture), 1934 (Reel 76, Frame 32)
    - International Workers School, 1933-1935 (Reel 76, Frame 45)
      - Duplicate copy, Micro 816 (Reel 45, Frame 512)
    - Leadership School, 1980, 1986, Micro 2050 (Reel 76, Frame 45)
    - Los Angeles Labor and Socialist School, undated (Reel 76, Frame 517)
    - Marxian Labor College bulletins (San Francisco), 1937-1938, Micro 596 (Reel 32, Othertype 25)
    - Marxist Labor School, 1935-1949, Micro 2050 (Reel 76, Frame 530)
    - Midwest Vacation School, 1944-1947 (Reel 76, Frame 538)
    - Mountain Spring Camp, 1949-1961, 1967, undated (Reel 76, Frame 651)
    - National Education Department
      - Basic training course, circa 1942, undated (Reel 76, Frame 650)
      - General publications, 1938-1974
        - Housing, by Grace Saunders, 1938, Micro 816 (Reel 45, Frame 833)
        - Bulletin on China, 1938, Micro 2050 (Reel 76, Frame 659)
        - ALP Bulletin, 1939 (Reel 76, Frame 669)
        - In Defense of Marxism, 1943 (Reel 76, Frame 6??)
        - The Lima Conference: Yankee Imperialism on the Offensive, 1939, Micro 816 (Reel 45, Frame 639)
        - Proletarian Military Policy, 1940, Micro 596 (Reel 32, Othertype 24)
          - Duplicate, Micro 816 (Reel 45, Frame 309)
        - The ALP and its Prospects, 1943, by John Fredericks (Reel 45, Frame 616)
          - Duplicate copy, Micro 2050 (Reel 76, Frame 680)
        - Bulletin of the [New York] Women's Committee, #1, 1943, Micro 816 (Reel 46, Frame 209)
        - Theses of Revolutionary Socialists on the Jewish Problem, 1944 (Reel 46, Frame 160)
        - Teachings of Leon Trotsky, 1944, by Jack Warwick, Micro 2050 (Reel 76, Frame 708)
        - Leon Trotsky on the Labor Party, 1948 (Reel 76, Frame 747)
        - Bibliography of published Trotsky writings in English Bulletins, 1955, 1959 (Reel 76, Frame 776)
        - African Revolution, 1961, Micro 816 (Reel 45, Frame 355)
        - Defending the Revolutionary Party and Its Perspectives, 1966 (Reel 45, Frame 560)
      - Marxist handbooks
        - ABC of Marxism, pre-1944, Micro 2050 (Reel 76, Frame 902)
          - Duplicate copy, Micro 816 (Reel 46, Frame 221)
        - The Truth About Kronstadt, undated, by John G. Wright, Micro 2050 (Reel 77, Frame 1)
      - Public speaking manuals and guides, 1933-1944, undated (Reel 77, Frame 526)
      - Study guides and outlines (chronological)
        - General, 1938-1976, undated, Micro 816 (Reel 48, Frame 1)
        - Trotsky on the Canadian Farmer, 1936, Micro 2050 (Reel 77, Frame 27)
        - Outline of History of Russian Bolshevism, 1940, by John G. Wright, Micro 596 (Reel 32, Othertype 24)
        - Summary of Education Talk on Stalinism, 1942, by Felix Morrow, Micro 2050 (Reel 77, Frame 30)
        - Dialectical Materialism, by William Warde, Micro 816 (Reel 45, Frame 547)
        - Questions and References for the Basic Training Course, 1944, Micro 2050 (Reel 77, Frame 33)
        - Greek Events and Its Lessons to the Working Class, 1944 (Reel 77, Frame 40)
        - What is Trotskyism?, pre-1944 by Jack Weber, Micro 816 (Reel 46, Frame 264)
        - Reference material on UAW-CIO, 1945, Micro 2050 (Reel 77, Frame 46)
        - Marxian Value and the Market, by Warren Creel, 1945 (Reel 77, Frame 49)
        - Fascism, by Chris Andrews, 1945, Micro 816 (Reel 45, Frame 547)
        - Educational materials, circa 1948, Micro 2050 (Reel 77, Frame 136)
        - Bibliography on fascism (Reel 77, Frame 138)
        - History of American Socialism, 1957 (Reel 77, Frame 141)
        - 1970-1980, 1988 (Reel 77, Frame 154)
        - Undated study guides
          - History of the Russian Revolution (Reel 77, Frame 144)
          - General undated guides (Reel 77, Frame 289)
      - Oberlin Educational Conferences, 1974-1987 (Reel 77, Frame 743)
      - School of International Socialism, 1967 (Reel 78, Frame 1)
      - Socialist Scholars Conferences, 1969-1970 (Reel 78, Frame 9)
      - Southern California Socialist Summer School, 1971 (Reel 78, Frame 27)
      - Summer schools
        - General, 1965-1974 (Reel 78, Frame 35)
        - Branch files (chronological, then alphabetical by city), 1961-1974 (Reel 78, Frame 164)
      - Trotsky Schools
        - Administrative correspondence, 1944, 1951-1962 (Reel 78, Frame 783)
        - Class materials and notes
          - 1954 (Reel 79, Frame 1)
          - 1955, 1961-1962 (Reel 80, Frame 1)
      - Unidentified educational material
        - Selected Reading in Marxism by Maurice Spector, 1932 (Reel 80, Frame 953)
        - Science, Dialectic and Bourgeois Society, 1953, by Arne Swabeck (Reel 80, Frame 1053)
        - The Role of the Revolutionary Party in History, 1954, by Theodore Edwards (?) (Reel 80, Frame 1093)
      - West Coast Vacation School
        - General, 1945-1963, undated (Reel 80, Frame 1246)
        - Three lectures by Murry Weiss, 1961 (Reel 80, Frame 1276)
  - Election Files
    - 1948
      - Brochures (Reel 81, Frame 1)
      - Manual draft (Reel 81, Frame 30)
      - Press material and publicity (Reel 81, Frame 40)
    - 1952
      - Brochures (Reel 81, Frame 264)
      - Press material and publicity, 1950-1952 (Reel 81, Frame 275)
    - 1956
      - Brochures (Reel 81, Frame 350)
      - Press material and publicity, 1953-1956 (Reel 81, Frame 363)
    - 1960
      - Brochures (Reel 81, Frame 405)
      - Correspondence (Reel 81, Frame 411)
      - Party Campaigner (Reel 81, Frame 511)
      - Press material and publicity (Reel 81, Frame 550)
    - 1968
      - Afro-Americans for Halstead-Boutelle (Reel 81, Frame 699)
      - Ballot drive notebook (Reel 81, Frame 719)
      - Bay Area committee (Reel 81, Frame 787)
      - Brochures (Reel 81, Frame 799)
      - Choice '68 (Reel 82, Frame 1)
      - Correspondence
        - General (Reel 82, Frame 57)
        - Halstead's overseas tour (Reel 82, Frame 97)
      - Local publications (Reel 82, Frame 334)
      - Minutes (Reel 82, Frame 381)
      - Miscellany (Reel 82, Frame 394)
      - New York State (Reel 82, Frame 421)
      - Press material and publicity, 1967-1968 (Reel 82, Frame 456)
      - Reports (Reel 82, Frame 912)
    - 1972
      - Brochures (Reel 83, Frame 1)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Reel 83, Frame 173)
      - Endorser Drive (Reel 83, Frame 261)
      - Miscellany (Reel 83, Frame 295)
      - Militant inserts (Reel 83, Frame 309)
      - Press material and publicity, 1971-1972 (Reel 83, Frame 330)
      - Report (Reel 84, Frame 1)
      - Youth newsletter (Reel 84, Frame 37)
    - 1976
      - Brochures (Reel 84, Frame 47)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Reel 84, Frame 320)
      - Handbook (Reel 84, Frame 420)
      - Minutes (Reel 84, Frame 445)
      - Miscellany (Reel 84, Frame 504)
      - Petition, Endorser drives (Reel 84, Frame 541)
      - Presidential slate questionnaires, 1974 (Reel 84, Frame 578)
      - Press material and publicity, 1974-1976 (Reel 84, Frame 620)
    - 1980
      - Brochures (Reel 85, Frame 1)
      - Correspondence (Reel 85, Frame 135)
      - Miscellany (Reel 85, Frame 146)
      - Press material and publicity, 1977-1980 (Reel 85, Frame 170)
    - 1984
      - Brochures (Reel 85, Frame 553)
      - Federal financial report forms (Reel 85, Frame 598)
      - Manual for local committees (Reel 85, Frame 881)
      - Miscellany (Reel 85, Frame 910)
      - Press material and publicity, 1981-1984 (Reel 85, Frame 929)
    - 1988
      - Brochures (Reel 86, Frame 1)
      - Correspondence (Reel 86, Frame 10)
      - Minutes (Reel 86, Frame 53)
      - Press material and publicity (Reel 86, Frame 158)
    - Initiative and referenda PC subcommittee correspondence, 1979-1982, 1988 (Reel 86, Frame 237)
  - Branch Correspondence
    - Akron, 1941-1954 (Reel 1, Frame 2)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1945-1949 (Reel 1, Frame 314)
    - Atlanta, 1969-1974 (Reel 1, Frame 358)
      - Atlanta Discussion Bulletin, 1977 (Reel 1, Frame 426)
    - At-large, 1968-1976 (Reel 1, Frame 442)
    - Austin, 1970-1973 (Reel 1, Frame 621)
    - Baltimore, 1946, 1949, 1961 (Reel 1, Frame 680)
    - Bayonne, New Jersey, 1944-1946 (Reel 1, Frame 700)
    - Boston
      - Correspondence
        - 1944-1961 (Reel 1, Frame 708)
        - 1964-1976, undated (Reel 2, Frame 1)
      - Discussion Bulletin, 1977-1978 (Reel 2, Frame 354)
    - Buffalo, 1942-1959 (Reel 2, Frame 453)
    - California, 1966 (Reel 2, Frame 718)
      - California Discussion Bulletin
        - 1982, February - March (Reel 2, Frame 724)
        - 1983, September - November (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - Chicago
      - Minutes and reports, 1944-1966 (Reel 3, Frame 97)
      - Correspondence
        - 1941-1953 (Reel 3, Frame 209)
        - 1954-1976 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
      - Chicago-Gary District Discussion Bulletin, 1980-1982 (Reel 4, Frame 547)
      - Chicago Local SWP Discussion Bulletin, 1977-1978 (Reel 4, Frame 670)
    - Cincinnati, 1944-1976 (Reel 4, Frame 795)
    - Cleveland
      - Minutes and reports, 1966-1974 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
      - Correspondence, 1944-1976 (Reel 5, Frame 125)
      - Scherr for Mayor campaign, 1973 (Reel 5, Frame 853)
    - Connecticut, 1961-1966 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - Denver
      - Minutes and reports, 1961-1975 (Reel 6, Frame 33)
      - Correspondence, 1958-1976 (Reel 6, Frame 103)
    - Detroit
      - Minutes and reports, 1944-1976 (Reel 6, Frame 488)
      - Correspondence
        - 1941-1944 (Reel 6, Frame 736)
        - 1945-1966 (Reel 7)
        - 1967-1977, undated (Reel 8, Frame 1)
      - Internal Discussion Bulletin, 1976-1977 (Reel 8, Frame 295)
      - Michigan Militant Newsletter, 1959-1961 (Reel 8, Frame 426)
    - Flint
      - 1940-1947, March (Reel 8, Frame 495)
      - 1947, April - 1953 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - Houston
      - Minutes and reports, 1971-1976 (Reel 9, Frame 255)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1976 (Reel 9, Frame 337)
      - Discussion Bulletin, 1977 (Reel 9, Frame 606)
    - Kansas City, 1945-1946 (Reel 9, Frame 655)
    - Los Angeles
      - Minutes and reports
        - 1939-1950 (Reel 9, Frame 701)
        - 1952-1976 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
      - Correspondence
        - 1939-1952 (Reel 10, Frame 296)
        - 1953-1965 (Reel 11)
        - 1966-1975 (Reel 12)
        - 1976 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
      - Miscellaneous campaigns, 1973 (Reel 13, Frame 141)
      - City Letters, 1944-1976 (Reel 13, Frame 175)
      - Internal Bulletin, 1946-1953 (Reel 13, Frame 435)
      - Discussion Bulletin
        - 1976-1977 (Reel 13, Frame 748)
        - 1978-1979 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
      - Young Militant/Young Socialist Reply, 1946-1963 (Reel 14, Frame 191)
    - Los Angeles East
      - Minutes and reports, 1974-1975 (Reel 14, Frame 215)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Reel 14, Frame 338)
      - Branch Letter, 1975 (Reel 14, Frame 497)
    - Los Angeles West
      - Minutes and reports, 1975 (Reel 14, Frame 568)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Reel 14, Frame 684)
      - Branch Letter, 1975-1976 (Reel 14, Frame 801)
    - Louisville, 1976 (Reel 14, Frame 817)
    - Miami, 1976 (Reel 14, Frame 834)
    - Milwaukee
      - 1943-1949 (Reel 14, Frame 836)
      - 1950-1976 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Minneapolis
      - Correspondence
        - 1929-1958 (Reel 15, Frame 324)
        - 1959-1983 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
      - Minnesota Discussion Bulletin, 1984 (Reel 16, Frame 600)
    - Missoula, Montana, 1945 (Reel 16, Frame 628)
    - Morgantown, West Virginia, 1947-1950 (Reel 16, Frame 632)
    - New Haven, Connecticut, 1947-1951 (Reel 16, Frame 696)
    - New Orleans, 1976 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - New York City
      - General
        - Minutes and internal convention bulletins
          - 1939-1951 (Reel 17, Frame 24)
          - 1952-1964 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
          - 1965-1975, undated (Reel 19, Frame 1)
        - Correspondence
          - 1933-1961 (Reel 19, Frame 411)
          - 1962-1989 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
        - Campaigner, 1948 (Reel 20, Frame 320)
        - City Letter, 1947-1971 (Reel 20, Frame 342)
        - Internal Discussion Bulletin, 1973-1978 (Reel 20, Frame 519)
        - Miscellaneous publications, 1943-1945 (Reel 20, Frame 870)
      - Brooklyn
        - Minutes, 1971-1975 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
        - Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Reel 21, Frame 254)
      - Lower Manhattan
        - Minutes, 1975 (Reel 21, Frame 374)
        - Correspondence, 1975 (Reel 21, Frame 508)
      - Upper West Side
        - Minutes, 1975 (Reel 21, Frame 598)
        - Correspondence, 1975 (Reel 21, Frame 698)
    - New York-New Jersey District
      - Report, 1983 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
      - Discussion Bulletin, 1984 (Reel 22, Frame 8)
    - Newark, New Jersey
      - Correspondence, 1944-1975, 1984 (Reel 22, Frame 179)
      - Workers' Voice and campaign material, 1938 (Reel 22, Frame 295)
    - Oakland-Berkeley, 1950-1976 (Reel 22, Frame 472)
    - Philadelphia, 1940-1976 (Reel 23, Frame 80)
    - Pittsburgh, 1947-1954 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - Portland, 1940-1976 (Reel 24, Frame 132)
    - Reading, Pennsylvania, 1942-1946 (Reel 24, Frame 251)
    - Richmond, Virginia, 1975-1976 (Reel 24, Frame 326)
    - Rochester, New York, 1944-1948 (Reel 24, Frame 346)
    - Salt Lake City, 1976 (Reel 24, Frame 393)
    - St. Louis, 1945-1975 (Reel 24, Frame 402)
    - San Diego, 1942-1964, 1972 (Reel 24, Frame 703)
    - San Francisco
      - Correspondence
        - 1939-1941, 1944-1946 (Reel 24, Frame 851)
        - 1947-1967 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
        - 1968-1976 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
      - Discussion Bulletin, 1947-1954, 1976-1977 (Reel 26, Frame 663)
    - San Jose, California, 1976 (Reel 27, Frame 151)
    - San Pedro, California, 1942-1944 (Reel 27, Frame 153)
    - Seaside, California, 1981-1983 (Reel 27, Frame 283)
    - Seattle
      - Correspondence, 1942-1973 (Reel 28, Frame 340)
      - Discussion Bulletin, 1953, #1 only (Reel 29, Frame 2)
    - Tacoma, 1946-1948 (Reel 29, Frame 41)
    - Texas, 1940, 1944, 1946-1947, 1949, See also Houston. (Reel 29, Frame 82)
    - Toledo, 1940, 1944-1952, 1975 (Reel 29, Frame 140)
    - Washington, D.C.
      - Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Reel 29, Frame 489)
      - Discussion Bulletin, 1977 (Reel 29, Frame 520)
    - Youngstown, Ohio, 1942-1958 (Reel 29, Frame 629)
  - Activities and Organizing Records
    - Anti-draft work, 1980-1985 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - Anti-nuclear work, 1977-1982 (Reel 30, Frame 69)
    - Anti-war work, 1965-1975
      - Defense cases (Reel 30, Frame 173)
      - Attorney General's list of subversives, 1948-1963 (Reel 30, Frame 340)
      - Berkeley students defense committee, 1968 (Reel 30, Frame 379)
      - Bernard, Leo
        - General, 1966-1967 (Reel 30, Frame 387)
        - Clippings, 1966-1967 (Reel 30, Frame 627)
      - Blanco, Hugo, 1963 (Reel 30, Frame 647)
      - Bombing of SWP National Office and Militant, 1966 (Reel 30, Frame 661)
      - Boudin, Kathy
        - General, 1981-1984 (Reel 30, Frame 756)
        - Clippings (Reel 30, Frame 859)
      - Central Michigan University
        - General, 1976-1977 (Reel 30, Frame 914)
        - Clippings, 1976-1977 (Reel 31, Frame 2)
      - Chicago Red Squad, 1975-1985 (Reel 31, Frame 71)
      - Customs harassment (Harris, Jaquith, Manuel, Mason), 1984-1989 (Reel 31, Frame 183)
      - Davis, Angela, 1971 (Reel 31, Frame 216)
      - Democratic Election Laws Committee (CoDEL), 1971-1976 (Reel 31, Frame 228)
      - Detroit SWP office bombing, 1946 (Reel 31, Frame 462)
      - Farinas, Juan, 1970-1972 (Reel 31, Frame 484)
      - Free assembly and political expression on campus
        - General, 1970-1973 (Reel 31, Frame 538)
        - Legal documents (Reel 31, Frame 842)
        - Clippings (Reel 32, Frame 2)
      - Freedom Socialist Party case, 1985 (Reel 32, Frame 29)
      - Freeway Hall Case Defense Committee, 1986-1988 (Reel 32, Frame 124)
      - GI defense
        - General, 1965-1975 (Reel 32, Frame 163)
        - SWP and YSA Members in the military (Reel 32, Frame 426)
      - House Un-American Activities Committee
        - General, 1965 (Reel 32, Frame 623)
        - Los Angeles
          - General, 1962 (Reel 32, Frame 636)
          - Clippings, 1962 (Reel 32, Frame 684)
        - USWA Local #2058, 1961-1962 (Reel 32, Frame 720)
      - Houston Committee to Defend Democratic Rights, 1971 (Reel 32, Frame 734)
      - Johnson, Joe, Deportation case, 1965-1966 (Reel 32, Frame 828)
      - Jonasco, John, Deportation case, 1957 (Reel 32, Frame 836)
      - Jones, Keith (GI Defense), 1968-1970 (Reel 33, Frame 2)
      - Jurenas, Ed (GI Defense), 1971 (Reel 33, Frame 21)
      - Kissing Case (Robert Williams), 1959 (Reel 33, Frame 109)
      - Knoxville 22 defense, 1971 (Reel 33, Frame 157)
      - Kolis, Salm, Committee to Defend, 1974 (Reel 33, Frame 221)
      - Kos, Walter (GI defense), 1966-1970 (Reel 33, Frame 372)
      - Los Angeles bombing (Political Rights Defense Fund), 1975 (Reel 33, Frame 476)
      - Lieberman, Jack (free speech at Florida State University), 1972 (Reel 33, Frame 612)
      - Mandel, Ernest, 1968-1978, undated (Reel 33, Frame 620)
      - Marroquin Manriquez, Hector (political asylum case), 1974-1989, undated (Reel 34, Frame 227)
      - Miles, Joe (GI defense), 1968-1970 (Reel 34, Frame 792)
      - Militant libel suit, 1952-1954 (Reel 35, Frame 3)
      - Miscellaneous defense cases, 1971-1976 (Reel 35, Frame 87)
      - Monroe Defendants, Committee to Aid
        - General, 1961-1964 (Reel 35, Frame 230)
        - Clippings and newsletters, 1962-1964 (Reel 35, Frame 526)
      - National Peace Action Coalition vs. House Internal Security Committee, 1971 (Reel 35, Frame 613)
      - National Steel and Shipbuilding Company (NASSCO) defense (Reel 35, Frame 593)
      - New York Headquarters bombing, 1969 (Reel 35, Frame 706)
      - New York Red Squad (Handshu case), 1980-1985 (Reel 35, Frame 714)
      - Ohio Un-American Activities, 1953, 1955 (Reel 35, Frame 884)
      - Petrick, Howard (GI defense), 1967-1971 (Reel 36, Frame 3)
      - Phillips, Wendell, Academic Freedom Committee, 1961-1964 (Reel 36, Frame 93)
      - Rosenberg Case, National Committee to Re-Open, 1975 (Reel 36, Frame 333)
      - Scythes, George Albert (deportation), 1961-1962 (Reel 36, Frame 397)
      - Selander, Ted (deportation), 1949-1950 (Reel 36, Frame 475)
      - Skoglund, Carl (deportation), 1949-1950 (Reel 36, Frame 506)
      - Sobell, Morton, Committee to Secure Justice for, 1958-1966 (Reel 36, Frame 520)
      - Starsky, Morris
        - General, 1969-1975 (Reel 36, Frame 543)
        - Clippings (Reel 36, Frame 752)
        - Legal documents (Reel 37, Frame 3)
      - Stryffler, Jim (GI defense), 1983-1984 (Reel 37, Frame 119)
      - Swett, Charles, 1950 (Reel 37, Frame 182)
      - Tate, Ernie, 1966-1967 (Reel 37, Frame 205)
      - Toame, Khalil, 1968 (Reel 37, Frame 243)
      - Trucks Law SWP on Michigan ballot, 1952 (Reel 37, Frame 272)